okay so now we go to the four formulas
rooms Laura vamos a las cuatro menos
sing for me
are they really formless realms a
Cassandra leads on Drano sinful man
Ronnie doesn't know no more cases can
know why yeah they cause the formless
realms they're not formless realms okay
the cost if you do that meditation a lot
and you die you will be born in the
formless ma'am okay son causa para Rana
sir Anand Raina's informa pero no son
Lorena's informa cuando en tres en este
tipo metas en simplemente general Oscars
para ser lo seat amore eras en ese
momento so here's some copper on the
four formulas rooms at estas some
carbons cuatro
Ramos informant by the way sometimes
they call them kitchy kitchy usually is
a book it's from Stanley Bundy spoke
that she is zoom Libra Stanley bandeau
it means the 18 categories significant
eight twelve twelve categories kihl-jae
las doce very categorical sorry twelve
doors of sense are called KJ doors I
sense it means the six objects six
powers and consciousness so six and six
six and six some laws say los cinco
proposals Cynthia's mass la conciencia
saan saan seis y los a so ghetto
Sandusky same in Sanskrit scholar
Donna and Sasuke to see ma attend but
sometimes they call the four formless
realm meditations KJ also okay so don't
be confused novices lamina los cuatro a
las vacaciones a las cuatro menos de
Lorean machine forma catching as he can
not confirm that okay so Michelle and am
katayaki KJ these have cute names nice
names
it's the somewhat anomalous some numbers
were values the names help you remember
the meditation los nombres the UN Accord
are tell America soon the first ones
called infinite space space with no end
in the space okay la primera CMS
position finito or spacio Sinn Fein
inconvenience soo-dong topic to share
apart on me do a young danyoung to
number shifting MCAT I saw me a douche a
Yong Yong Yong to combat Chevy Russia to
certain mental capacity but intent on
Chapel oh there's the definition event
okay
I even elephants yawn during the fourth
formula meditations durante las cuatro
menos in the reign of former we were
focusing on the heart right nos concept
Ramos en el corazon and there was some
awareness of physical the physical heart
yell concentrate a in el corazon in
conciencia del corazon physical then as
you go into formless meditation yell
swimmer here toe and are dentro de la my
personal trainers informal you're gonna
take the heart okay Massa who's el
corazon and you're gonna let it break
down and dissolve us hacer que el
corazon en el cortecito CFO condo
problem ain't a silly swirl so we'll
start at the heart the film sacraments
are en el corazon beating heart the
Corazon
love the end or Corazon physicality
awareness of some piece of meat in your
chest right sir la conciencia de se
Perez Ricard men to the poquito and
patron to Hue el corazon and then the
transition is very similar to the air
conditioner to the heart Ella transition
Casas de se Corazon fisico Conte Hedo
molecular illness in Toledo similar
Allah transition Casas the lady a
condition odd o Allah t el corazon so if
you're teaching it you have to say now
compare your heart hace casi lo and st.
see two incisions estimate asian tienes
que hacer ahora con para tu corazon
physical - and the space con el espacio
finito so between those two steps and
presses those passes at the first step
of the formula in el cuarto Paso del Rey
NOLA Foreman still she is a standard tu
corazon as you go into the formless
realm meditations an intravenous meet as
soon as the dream is informal let your
heart break down like a sand castle the
water gets to the sand castle and it
starts to thaw chorus permitir que tu
Corazon series well wha come on Castillo
de reina cake on streets take on the
lady ago a lowly a Hail Mary lava this
all viendo s arena no commute a NS plus
infinite like a sugar cube that gets wet
you know
come on Kuya so Curtis emotion so you're
gonna focus on your heart it wasn't for
cutting to Corazon then let that it's
called here the the picture of
physicality in your mind aqui es cuando
oven donas lima him allah conception the
physically death and two men taken to
maintain this world was not physically
that and let that idea physicality
these are just as soon re solution
d'leh physically da and that pole the US
Pacific Command el corazon Latino Kanta
he doe then for me what comes next
it always felt like to me like
horizontal I don't know why yeah para me
no support chaos in presence nto como
listen Dan is wanted no supporting the
heart dissolves like sugar el corazon
series solo como Ella super container
mine just stretches out infinitely
because infinitely it never stops okay
ela meant a 16-day Asiata Lin finito in
secant emerge the nemesis in nunca para
nós esse so it's a feeling of like you
just start spreading and you keep going
and you never stop okay s nasan's a co
no sentimentality expand as expands
expands a continuous CC ba CC AC CC no
casa para no casa para continue continue
as wide as the universe in dalek
Stanzione totally al universe infinite
okay let's join we don't have a lot of
time I'm trying to let's try to go there
we're gonna go we're gonna watch the
breath they were gonna dissolve the
heart my keen Tatar Latinos poco tiempo
vans are observable ah respiration
yo hago Mousavi solar el corazon what's
the condition of the body in condiciones
del cuerpo an estimate assume nam
anesthetized
elk or post a nest a sea otter what's
the emotion
kamo seein teenis nothing nothing
yeah unemotional also anesthetized
tambien estan to say mo Sione's Astana
nest a cialis no sympathy when anima
lastest but there should be this
sensation of
the heart desires and the mind starts to
just leak as as far as space okay Yona
resistance AC on the resolution Delta
here chorus Anfisa co e to maintain 16 l
set allows me by the way this this last
we did for so far right we did five if
you count the air conditioner out the
desire realm
I'm also chose Cinco minutos in sequent
Islamic agenda later conditionally no
lesser we did five if you count a desire
Ram
CMOS in cosecant of La Salle renal de
sel now we're gonna do six realms and
Cersei's but just to give you a heads up
after where we're going in solo para and
TC powerless as Yolanda knows it he mows
when you do the lion stance when the
torus is Leland's early on maybe the
whole thing takes an hour gondolas
Lancel young Muslims to I you are and
you don't throw aura but do not a not a
thing us you don't stop you go you go
from one you go from air conditioner
buzzes the lighter conditional for los
cuatro novellas el drano la forma for
yellow squat renewal is el drano enough
for my Singapore then purposely
you come back y SE se requried o por lo
que por el drano la forma passes already
no sin for master Luke or Tony belly a
propósito regresses the drain olesen
forma and reno the la forma that's a lie
that's most of the lion stance
okay SES casa da da la danse early on
but you're gonna have to do something
over here
para que el final de las que ser algo
you get a park here for a while
Davis esta señor aquí en esta parte
there's something beyond the form
I yell go it's tamasa yeah and I know
Ellis important okay just to give you a
preview yes estoy MPC panel okay Melanie